Support Admin Watch on
kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
(Gemini)
(Episode 5)
Stop her!
You lied to me.
You humiliated me.
You betrayed me.
I curse you all to have a miserable death.
- Save her! - You will be denied...
reincarnation in death.
If there's a next life,
I will skin you alive, tear your tendons,
and reduce your bones to dust.
This is bad. The formation is broken.
Tell me.
What's going on?
Perhaps, while I was casting the spell,
someone else bound to Master Xiao by fate...
offered their life as a sacrifice...
to call to her.
Thus, the Master's soul...
went astray,
and she was resurrected through a corpse.
Resurrected through a corpse?
Where is she?
If Master...
has possessed someone's body,
I... I'm afraid...
she's lost all her memories.
Amidst this vast crowd, she’s lost all memory.
How am I supposed to find her?
On the left shoulder of the person Master possessed,
a blood-colored orchid will bloom.
If we use this as a guide,
we can find Master's real body.
I'll find you.
From heaven to hell,
you can't hide from me.
(Xuntian Sect)
Chief.
The Emperor has issued an order.
You'll take over as the master of the Xuntian Sect.
Alright.
If you don't eat or sleep,
your body won't be able to take it.
If you collapse,
who will avenge Master Xiao?
Has Sis had such a hard time before?
By the way,
there's something else I want to tell you.
A while ago,
the Princess of Chu slipped and fell at her birthday banquet.
But there was no funeral at the King of Chu's manor.
Our spy just sent us a tip-off today.
The Princess of Chu, who was bound to die.
Actually came back to life.
Is this true?
Yes.
Perhaps, while I was casting the spell,
someone else bound to Master Xiao by fate...
Thus, the Master's soul...
went astray,
and she was resurrected through a corpse.
I've given my orchid jade pendant...
to the Princess of Chu, Lu Zhao.
I promised to help her.
Is she alive?
How... How is that possible?
The fall at Zhaoyue Pavilion didn't kill her.
They said she looked dead.
I don't know what happened,
but she suddenly came back to life.
It's just that...
she hasn't regained consciousness.
How persistent.
But it's better this way.
We wouldn't want a delay in His Highness' plans.
It's just that...
I can't bear this anger inside me.
That's right.
She humiliated His Highness...
in front of so many people.
She deserves to die.
Tell me.
When a person falls from a high place,
it's inevitable for them...
to break their bones and get disfigured.
Am I right?
You're right.
I'm on it.
Xiao Jin Yu.
Where am I?
Who are you?
Who am I?
With my body,
I sustain your soul.
From now on,
You are me.
Lu Zhao.
Lu Zhao?
When you wake up,
your past will be gone.
When it's gone,
you will live as me.
You will have my memories.
That includes...
my hatred.
Where will I go then?
With body and soul divided,
the future remains uncertain.
If you want to regain your memories...
and find your true self,
you need to let go of your attachments.
My attachments?
Remember.
Let those who wronged others reap what they sow.
Bring total ruin to the traitor, in both body and honor.
A divorce letter...
shall appease the departed.
Sis.
Why did you take so long to cut her face?
Keep it down.
You're giving me a headache.
You... Lu Zhao.
You...
You killed Du Juan.
It's you.
Since you're so worried about her,
why don't I send you to be with her down there?
You're not Lu Zhao.
You can't be Lu Zhao.
Who are you?
Who am I?
Of course, I'm an evil spirit from hell.
Didn't anyone tell you?
If you do too many bad things,
you'll see ghosts.
From now on,
I'll be your nightmare.
I'll make you...
sleep restlessly every night.
Go to hell!
Liu Ying Xue!
What are you doing?
Your Highness.
She... She's a ghost!
Your Highness!
She killed Du Juan.
She tried to kill me too.
Save me, Your Highness!
I didn't!
Your Highness.
My dear.
I had a splitting headache as soon as I woke up.
I don't remember anything.
Do you really not know...
how you got hurt...
and how you ended up here?
Do you not remember anything?
I don't remember anything.
I only remember...
that you're my husband.
What about the body?
When I woke up,
I saw...
a dark shadow...
darting past the window.
Then,
a knife flew by.
I was so scared.
That lady...
came running in.
She said...
I'm the killer.
She wants me to pay with my life.
Your Highness.
I'm scared.
You're lying.
That's not true.
You killed Du Juan.
- You even tried to kill me! - Miss.
I... I'm just a lady.
How could I kill someone with a knife?
Why would you accuse me?
You wench!
Are you done?
- Come here. - Your Highness.
Your Highness!
It's a blow to the neck.
It's an instant death.
This is a common technique used by assassins.
But you said it was Lu Zhao's doing.
Go back to your room.
Don't cause any more trouble.
Wait.
She said...
there was an assassin in her room.
Why don't you ask her...
where the assassin is?
Your Highness.
Stay in your room.
Don't leave.
My dear!
My dear.
- My dear. - Your Highness.
Calm down.
I'll be right back.
Be careful, my dear.
Your Highness.
My dear.
Since you're here,
why don't you show yourself?
She still has the moves.
However, her inner power is gone.
Sis.
It really is you.
Who are you?
Princess of Chu.
I'm a friend, not an enemy.
I'm here to help you.
Help me?
Why are you helping me?
The jade pendant you're wearing...
was given to you by Xiao Jin Yu, the master of the Xuntian Sect.
Seeing the jade pendant is like seeing the master.
It's my duty to help you.
Besides,
we have a common enemy.
Situ Xian.
That's right.
The Xuntian Sect has been secretly investigating...
Prince of Chu's collaboration with the enemy.
If you don't want to get involved,
I can send you away right now.
No. I won't leave.
I want them to pay for what they did.
I want those who deceived me...
to pay for what they did.
Traitors...
will be ruined.
The enemy of my enemy...
is my ally.
Let's seal the oath with a handshake.
As of today,
our partnership begins.
From now on,
I'll be your sword.
Wait.
What's your name?
Xiao Ren.
The same "Xiao" as Xiao Jin Yu,
and "Ren" as in "towering and limitless".
What does this orchid...
signify?
With body and soul divided,
the future remains uncertain.
If you want to regain your memories...
and find your true self,
you need to let go of your attachments.
Is breaking free from my attachments...
the only way to reveal the other secrets?